Sharing Christmas is a romance, tv movie film directed by Peter Sullivan.
A real estate developer is given the opportunity of his career to
transform an old shopping complex into a prime location.
Unfortunately, there is one tenant who is holding out—the Christmas
shop owner he met by happenstance just days ago.
Stephanie, played by Ellen Hollman.
Michael, played by Bobby Campo.
Himself, played by Dave Koz.
Helen, played by Cynthia Gibb.
Patty, played by Melanie Nelson.
Dan, played by David Starzyk.
Many Christmas stories have been adapted to feature films and TV specials,
and have been broadcast and repeated many times on television.
Since the popularization of home video in the 1980s, these films are sold
and re-sold every year during the holiday shopping season.
Many television networks, film studios, and production companies, such as cable television channels Hallmark and Lifetime, produce and
release new Christmas-themed films every year during or around December, all with variations of similar plots and themes.
Additionally, films revolving around the Nativity story of Christmas are regularly
produced such as The Nativity Story (2006) and The Star (2017).
One film that has become the flashpoint for "Is this a Christmas movie or not?" debates is Die Hard (1988), with some viewing the film as a
Christmas movie intertwined with an action genre setting or a film that is simply set around the Christmas and holiday season.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.